Guide to the Time Inc. Time Editorial Records 1938-2009 MS 3009-RG 7
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.B. Executive Editor Edward Jamieson Files, 1957-1986; 37 Linear feet in 37 record cartons
  - Subseries II.B.2. Subject Files, 1957-1985; 17.75 Linear feet in 19 record cartons
    - 1970: Kennedy, Edward: Cover Correspondence (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 32)
    - 1970: Khrushchev, Nikita (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 33)
    - 1970: Lee, Alwyn: Death (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 34)
    - 1970: Maps (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 35)
    - 1970: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 36-38)
    - 1970: A Matter of Manner: Fragments from Time (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 39)
    - 1970: Navone, John: Seattle University (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 5)
    - 1970: New Forces in American Journalism (Offsite-box 3252, Folder 40)
    - 1970: Newsstand Sales Charts, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 1)
    - 1970: Newsweek / Time Business Sections (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 2)
    - 1970: Power of Print II (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 3)
    - 1970: Restaurant Associates Bills (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 4)
    - 1970: Russian File (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 5)
    - 1970: Steering Committee (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 6)
    - 1970: Time-Life Books (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 7)
    - 1970: Time / Newsweek Comparisons (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 8)
    - 1970: Time / Newsweek Monthly Sales (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 9)
    - 1970: Time / Newsweek Paper: Don Barr Memo (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 10)
    - 1970: Typewriter Information (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 11)
    - 1970: Vishniak, Mark (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 12)
    - 1971: Bank Covers (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 7)
    - 1971: Budget (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 13-14)
    - 1971: Business Covers (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 15)
    - 1971: Business and the Economy from Time/Canada, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 16)
    - 1971: Business Section Futures List (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 17)
    - 1971: Chaliapin, Boris: Consultant [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1971: Color Projects (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 18)
    - 1971: Consumer Magazine Advertising Scorecard, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 19)
    - 1971: Cover Artists (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 20)
    - 1971: Cover Booklet (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 21)
    - 1971: Cover Ideas (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 22)
    - 1971: Cover Schedules (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 23)
    - 1971: Davidson, Ralph: Timber Industry (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 24)
    - 1971: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 25-27)
    - 1971: Editorial Promotion (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 28)
    - 1971: Election Issue (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 29)
    - 1971: Essays: Abortion (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 30)
    - 1971: Essays: Lists (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 31)
    - 1971: Essays: Metaphysics of Time (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 32)
    - 1971: Essays: The Art and Science of Friendly Wagering (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 33)
    - 1971-1976: Essays Scrapbook (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 8)
    - 1971: Expenses and Reports (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 34-35)
    - 1971: Facts and Figures on 1970 Mail (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 36)
    - 1971: 52-Week Simulation Run (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 37)
    - 1971: Five Year Edit Review (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 38)
    - 1971: Five Year Plan (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 39-40)
    - 1971: FYI (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 41)
    - 1971: Judson, Horace: Election Year Box Proposal (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 42)
    - 1971: Iranian Ad Section (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 43)
    - 1971: Japan: Mishima's Suicide, 1970 (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 44)
    - 1971: Legal: Marcos v. Time (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 45)
    - 1971: "Lenny" Ad (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 46)
    - 1971: Lex Fundamentalis: Religion (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 47)
    - 1971: Magazines Received by Jamieson, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 48)
    - 1971: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 49-51)
    - 1971: Newsstand Sales (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 52)
    - 1971: Newstour: Report on America (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 53)
    - 1971: Offices (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 54)
    - 1971: Picture Procurement Costs (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 55)
    - 1971: Report on Black-Related News Coverage (Offsite-box 3253, Folder 56)
    - 1971: Simmons Figures: Time / Newsweek Comparisons (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 1)
    - 1971: Subscriber Delivery Report (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 2)
    - 1971: Symposium on Abortion (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 3)
      Includes transcripts.
    - 1971: Time Board of Economists Remarks (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 4)
    - 1971: Time Inc. Operating Statements (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 5)
    - 1971: Time-Life Books and Time Capsules (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 6)
    - 1971: Time-Life Bureau Lists (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 7)
    - 1971: Time-Life News Service Operating Statement (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 8)
    - 1971: Time / Newsweek Comparisons (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 9)
    - 1971: Time / Newsweek Editorial 4-Color (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 10)
    - 1971: Translator of Solzhenitsyn Extract (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 11)
    - 1971: Werner, Lucy (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 12)
    - 1971: Women's Liberation at Time (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 13)
    - 1972: Adler, Mortimer: Lecture (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 9)
    - 1972: Affirmative Action Program (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 14)
    - 1972: Arbatov, Georgi: United States Institute Moscow (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 10)
    - 1972: Bank Covers (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 11)
    - 1972: Bank Covers (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 15)
    - 1972: Biz Errors (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 16)
    - 1972: Budget: Corporate (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 17)
    - 1972: Budget: Covers (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 18)
    - 1972: Budget: Edit Raises (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 19)
    - 1972: Budget: Two-Year Plan (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 20)
    - 1972: Clifford Irving Cover (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 21)
    - 1972: Computer Space (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 22)
    - 1972: Copy Flow Chart (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 12)
    - 1972: Cover (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 13)
    - 1972: Cover Changes (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 23)
    - 1972: Cover List: 1923-1963 (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 14)
    - 1972: Current Form Close (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 24-25)
    - 1972: Daniel Yankelovich, Inc.: Election Campaign Research (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 26)
    - 1972: Democratic Convention Supplement (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 27)
    - 1972: Dixon, Jeane: Predictions (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 15)
    - 1972: Donnelley Crew Scheduling (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 16)
    - 1972: Donovan, Hedley: Speech at Sales Association of the Paper Industry (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 28)
    - 1972: Early Close (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 29)
    - 1972: Editing for the '70s (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 30)
    - 1972: Editorial Change Account (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 31)
    - 1972: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 32-33)
    - 1972: Editorial Services (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 34)
    - 1972: Editorial Top Editing Closing (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 35)
    - 1972: Election Night Staff (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 36)
    - 1972: Errors: Editorial Changes (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 37)
    - 1972: Essays: Bicentennial Commission (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 38)
    - 1972: Essays: China (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 39)
    - 1972: Essays: Economy (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 40)
    - 1972: Essays: Growth (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 41)
    - 1972: Essays: The New Cult of Madness (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 42)
    - 1972: Essays: New Left (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 43)
    - 1972: Essays: Possibilities (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 44)
    - 1972: Essays: Technology (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 45)
    - 1972: Essays: Vietnam (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 46)
    - 1972: Essays: What Things Cost (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 47)
    - 1972: Expenses (Offsite-box 3254, Folder 48-50)
    - 1972: Friedrich, Otto (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 1)
    - 1972: Gallagher Report: Adpage Figures (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 17)
    - 1972: Gart, Murray: Complaints on Time-Life News Service (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 18)
    - 1972: Gart, Murray: New Offices (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 19a)
    - 1972: Gart, Murray: Newsdesk Operation (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 19b)
    - 1972: Holiday Closings (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 2-4)
    - 1972: Howard Hughes Business Story and File, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 5-8)
    - 1972: Income Story (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 20)
    - 1972: Issue Close (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 9)
    - 1972: Jobs: African Americans (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 10)
    - 1972: Judson, Horace: Proposal to Reorganize Communications (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 21)
    - 1972: J. Walter Thompson Business Story (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 11)
    - 1972: Legal Cases (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 12)
    - 1972: Life Editorial (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 13)
    - 1972: Life Magazine Data (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 22)
    - 1972: Long Range Planning (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 14)
    - 1972: Man of the Year, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 23-24)
    - 1972: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 25-26)
    - 1972: Measure to Streamline Production Operation (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 27)
    - 1972: Minority Employment Review by Office of Federal Contract Compliance (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 15)
    - 1972: New Blood Memo (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 16)
    - 1972: New Minimum Schedules: New Contract Settlements (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 28)
    - 1972: News Cables (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 29)
    - 1972: Newspaper Guild Meeting Minutes (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 17-21)
    - 1972: Newsstand Sales Estimates (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 22)
    - 1972: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 30)
    - 1972: New Steer (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 23)
    - 1972: Newsweek Close (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 24)
    - 1972: Office Moves (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 25)
    - 1972: Olympic Fast Color and Supplement Page (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 26-27)
    - 1972: Outstanding Stories (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 31)
    - 1972: Page Budget, Color, and Goals (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 28-30)
    - 1972: Paris Letters (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 32)
    - 1972: Personnel Evaluation Meeting (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 33)
    - 1972: Petty Cash Slips (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 34)
    - 1972: Picture Counts (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 31)
    - 1972: Plastic Furniture Controversy (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 35)
    - 1972: Political Conventions: Democratic (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 36)
    - 1972: Political Conventions: Republican (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 37)
    - 1972: Political Conventions: Staff (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 38)
    - 1972: Pre-Olympic Supplement (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 32)
    - 1972: Publishing Week Memos (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 33)
    - 1972: Queries: Ben Cate (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 34)
    - 1972: Reader's Digest Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1972: Reader's Digest Payments (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 35)
    - 1972: Regional Editions of Time (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 36)
    - 1972: Research System (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 39)
    - 1972: Schecter, Jerry: A Letter to Hanoi (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 40)
    - 1972: Security Pages (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 37)
    - 1972: The Sexes Section (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 41)
    - 1972: Special Supplements (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 38)
    - 1972: Staff Cover Conference (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 42)
    - 1972: Subscriber Delivery Report (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 39)
    - 1972: Subscriber Research (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 40-41)
    - 1972: Text Syndication: Puerto Rico (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 42)
    - 1972: Time Asia (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 43-44)
    - 1972: Time Edit in Europe Report (Offsite-box 2444, Folder 43)
    - 1972: Time Inc. Operating Statement (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 45)
    - 1972: Time-Life Video (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 46)
    - 1972: Time / Newsweek Newsstand and Weekly Sales (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 47-48)
    - 1972: Time Pieces (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 49)
      Time Pieces was an internal journal about the magazine and staff similar to the corporoate newsletter F.Y.I..
    - 1972: Time: Schedule (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 1)
    - 1972: Time: United States Cover Comparison (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 2)
    - 1972: Trip: Mr. and Mrs. Jamieson Trip Folder (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 3)
    - 1972: Valentin, Betty: Temporary Assistant (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 4)
    - 1972: Vega, Marylois: Amfac, Inc. (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 5)
    - 1972: Videocomp Startup (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 50)
    - 1972: Washington and News Bureau Reorganization Notes (Offsite-box 3255, Folder 51)
    - 1972: Werner, Lucy (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 6)
    - 1972: Women's File: New York State Division of Human Rights (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 7)
    - 1972: Women's Issue (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 1)
    - 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 8)
    - 1973: Administration and Press Cover (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 9)
    - 1973: Affirmative Action Program (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 10)
    - 1973: Alcoa-Harper Letter (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 11)
    - 1973: Assistant Instructions (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 12)
    - 1973: Atlantic Edition (ATLO) (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 13)
    - 1973: Auer, Bernard: Yale Students for Interviews (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 14)
    - 1973: Black-and-white Page Cost (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 15)
    - 1973: Budget (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 16)
    - 1973: Business Railroad Article (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 17)
    - 1973: Close of Time Edit (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 18)
    - 1973: Closing Schedule By Section (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 19-20)
    - 1973: Color Proofs (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 21)
    - 1973: Cover Conference (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 22)
    - 1973: Cover Engraving Bills (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 23)
    - 1973: Cover Sales (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 24)
    - 1973: Cover Schedule (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 25)
    - 1973: Cut Quality (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 26)
    - 1973: Dateline (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 27)
    - 1973: Economy Review (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 28)
    - 1973: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 2)
    - 1973: Editorial Page (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 29)
    - 1973: Energy (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 30)
    - 1973: Energy Conference '73 (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 3)
    - 1973: Essay on Autos (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 31)
    - 1973: Essay on Cities (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 32)
    - 1973: Essay Memoranda from Ron Kriss (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 33)
    - 1973: Essay on Ethics (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 34)
    - 1973: European Board of Economists (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 35)
    - 1973: European Editorial Budget (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 36)
    - 1973: European Supplement (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 37)
    - 1973: Evaluations: Memorandum to Senior Editors (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 38)
    - 1973: Excess Costs (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 39)
    - 1973: Expense Account (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 40)
    - 1973: Expense Account (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 4)
    - 1973: 50th Anniversary (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 41-43)
    - 1973: Friedrich Lede on Watergate (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 44)
    - 1973: Gemstone (Watergate) (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 45)
    - 1973: Grunwald, Henry: Editorial: The President Should Resign (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 46)
    - 1973: Head Counts (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 47-48)
    - 1973: Humbard, Rex: Business Story (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 49)
    - 1973: "Journey to Ixtlan" (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 50)
    - 1973: July 4th Vote (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 51)
    - 1973: Library (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 52)
    - 1973: Life Employment [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1973: Map Room (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 53)
    - 1973: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2445, Folder 54-55)
    - 1973: Music Section (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 1)
    - 1973: New Perceptions in Sciences and Social Sciences (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 2)
    - 1973: New Researchers [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R39)
    - 1973: News Clips (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 3)
    - 1973: Newspaper Guild (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 4-5)
    - 1973: Newsweek: International (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 6)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Pack with Union (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 7)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: General (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 8-9)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Editorial Close Report (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 10)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Editorial Insert Page Volume (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 11)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Four Color Editorial (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 12)
    - 1973: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Share of Market (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 13-14)
    - 1973: Occidental Petroleum Corporation (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 15)
    - 1973: Operating Statement (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 16-18)
    - 1973: Page Budget (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 5)
    - 1973: Publicity Release (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 19)
    - 1973: Salary Administration Proposals (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 20)
    - 1973: Science: New View of Man (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 21)
    - 1973: Service Reductions (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 22)
    - 1973: Siberia Article (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 23)
    - 1973: State Department Foreign Journalist Exchange (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 24)
    - 1973: Study of Time Subscriber Attitudes (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 6)
    - 1973: Target Audience: Reactions to Time Cover Alternatives (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 25)
    - 1973: Three Year Plan (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 26)
    - 1973: Time/Canada Board of Economists Meeting (Offsite-box 3256, Folder 7)
    - 1973: Time: United States Sales Estimates (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 27)
    - 1973: Time Asia (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 28)
    - 1973: Time Inc.: Annual Report (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 29)
    - 1973: Time Inc.: Prospectus (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 30)
    - 1973: Time Pacific (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 31)
    - 1973: 24th Floor Moves (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 32)
    - 1973: United States Editions of Time Chart (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 34)
    - 1973: Vacation Policy (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 35)
    - 1973: Vega, Marylois: Time Editorial Morgue (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 36)
    - 1973: What To Do (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 37)
    - 1973: Women (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 38)
    - 1973: Women on Time Covers (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 39)
    - 1973: Writing Trials (Offsite-box 2446, Folder 40)
    - 1974: Ad Rates (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 1)
    - 1974: Art Park (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 2)
    - 1974: African Americans at Time (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 3)
    - 1974: Alcohol and Drug Abuse (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 4)
    - 1974: Back of Book Runs (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 5)
    - 1974: Bank Covers (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 6)
    - 1974: Bicentennial (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 7-10)
    - 1974: Billings of Japan's Hakuhodo Advertising Agency (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 11)
    - 1974: Black-and-white and Color Pages (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 12)
    - 1974: Board of Economists Lunch (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 13)
    - 1974: Books taken on Vacation (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 14)
    - 1974: Budget, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 15-17)
    - 1974: Business Section Staff (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 18)
    - 1974: Close Dates for Color (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 19)
    - 1974: Conflict of Interest (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 20)
    - 1974: Contributing Editors (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 21)
    - 1974: Copyright Policy (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 22)
    - 1974: Correspondents Interchange After Merger (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 23)
    - 1974: Cover Conference (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 24)
    - 1974: Cover: Pan Am (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 25)
    - 1974: Cover Research Project (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 26)
    - 1974: Cover Schedule (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 27)
    - 1974: Cover Subjects (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 28)
    - 1974: Cover Suggestions (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 29-31)
    - 1974: Cover Testing (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 32)
    - 1974: Disability and Discrimination (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 33)
    - 1974: Energy (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 34)
    - 1974: Essays (Offsite-box 2447, Folder 35-36)
    - 1974: Essays (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 1-4)
    - 1974: Essay: Death Wish (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 5)
    - 1974: Europe Editorial (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 6)
    - 1974: Europe: Rademaekers Memoranda (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 7)
    - 1974: Expense Account (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 8)
    - 1974: Foreign Policy Meeting in Washington (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 9-10)
    - 1974: Investigation of Time's European Subscribers (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 11)
    - 1974: Leadership Issue (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 12)
    - 1974: Little Brown Special Projects: Magaback and Magatext (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 13)
    - 1974: Man of the Year: Unused (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 14-15)
    - 1974: Masthead Changes (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 16-18)
    - 1974: Newspaper Guild (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 19)
    - 1974: Newsstand Sales Figures (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 20)
    - 1974: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Cover Comparisons (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 21-22)
    - 1974: Newsweek: Time vs. Newsweek: Staff Comparisons (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 23)
    - 1974: The Pacific: Future (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 24)
    - 1974: Personnel Policy (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 25)
    - 1974: Pines Oxford (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 26)
    - 1974: Schlesinger, James: Dinner (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 27)
    - 1974: Smith, Adam: Business Section (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 28)
    - 1974: Staff Evaluations (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 29-30)
    - 1974: Sunday Standby Contact List (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 31)
    - 1974: Supplementary Employee Confirmation Form (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 32)
    - 1974: Time Asia (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 33)
    - 1974: Trip: Travel Itinerary (Offsite-box 2448, Folder 34)
    - 1974: Wallace, George: Interview (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 1)
    - 1974: Warren, Earl: Obituary (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 2)
    - 1974: Well for B and B (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 3)
    - 1974: Women (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 4)
    - 1974: Writers and Researchers (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 5-6)
    - 1974: Yankelovich Time Feature: Public Trends (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 7)
    - 1975: Allen, Oliver: United Fund (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 8)
    - 1975: American Express Briefings (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 9)
    - 1975: American Express Newsletter (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 10)
    - 1975: Asia Coverage (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 11)
    - 1975: Bachman, Harriet: "That" Controversy (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 12)
    - 1975: Bank Covers [empty] (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 13)
    - 1975: Bicentennial (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 14-17)
    - 1975: Budget (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 18-20)
    - 1975: Cape Cod (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 21)
    - 1975: Color Futures (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 22)
    - 1975: Color Layout (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 23)
    - 1975: Copy Sales: Time Atlantic (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 24)
    - 1975: Covers: Britain: Henry Grunwald Memorandum (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 25)
    - 1975: Covers: Coal (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 26)
    - 1975: Covers: Conference [empty] (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 27)
    - 1975: Covers: Henry Grunwald on Asia Covers (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 28)
    - 1975: Covers: Report (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 29)
    - 1975: Covers: Sales (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 30)
    - 1975: Covers: Schedule (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 31-33)
    - 1975: Covers: Suggestions (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 34-35)
    - 1975: Covers: Switches and Color (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 36)
    - 1975: Covers: Testing [empty] (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 37)
    - 1975: Covers: USIA (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 38)
    - 1975: Current File (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 39)
    - 1975: Editorial Awards (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 40)
    - 1975: Editorial Task Force (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 41)
    - 1975: Employees Pictured in Publisher Letter (Offsite-box 2449, Folder 42)